Guide to the Charles E. Palm papers,1956-1986.
Palm, Charles E. papers,1956-1986.
  - Resident Instruction. Stutz, Frederick H.; Hertel, John P.; Malone, Veronica; Watkins, Thomas C.; Weiser, Josejf; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept, of Rural Education; New York State College of Agriculture, Office of Resident Instruction., 1960-1961 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Rural Education. Stutz, Frederick H.; Feldhusen, John; Leagans, J. Paul; Zien, Dewitt; Bail, Joe P.; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept, of Rural Education., 1960-1961 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Rural Sociology. Larson, Olaf F.; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept, of Rural Sociology., 1960-1961 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Safety Division. Barrett, John E., 1960-1961 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Salaries., 1960-1961 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Comparative Salary Information., 1960-1961 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Scholarship Committee, College of Agriculture., 1960-1961 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Space Committee., 1960-1961 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Statistical Quality Control Workshop. Buck, Paul A., 1960-1961 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Student Organization Luncheon with Dean, Directors, Department Heads., 1960-1961 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Space Assignments., 1960-1961 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Summer Session., 1960-1961 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Summer Training Program for Foreign Students Committee. Rockefeller Foundation., 1960-1961 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Vegetable Crops. Munger, Henry M.; Smith, Orrin E.; Smith, Ora; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept, of Vegetable Crops., 1960-1961 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - New York State Veterinary College. Poppensiek, George C., 1960-1961 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - New York State Veterinary College. New York State Veterinary College, Council., 1960-1961 (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - Professor Wimsatt, Confidential. Wimsatt, William A.; Gilbert, Perry W.; Anderson, John M.; Leonard, Samuel L., 1960-1961 (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - A Miscellaneous. Beef cattle., 1960-1961 (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - Morton Adams. Adams, Morton; New York State College of Agriculture, Council; New York State Agricultural Businessmen's Council., 1960-1961 (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - AGFU. Barton, Donald W.; Duncan, Spencer G., 1960-1961 (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - Agri-Businessmen's Council. Adams, Morton; New York State Agricultural Businessmen's Council., 1960-1961 (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - Agricultural Research, "New Horizons for Customers"., 1960-1961 (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - "Agriculture's New Dimensions.", 1960-1961 (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - Agricultural Research Institute. Johnson, Burt; Krauss, R.E., 1960-1961 (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - Agricultural Science Program. Watkins, Thomas C.; Tom, Frederick K.T.; Hill, Charles W.; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept, of Rural Education., 1960-1961 (Box 8, Folder 41)
  - Agriculture's New Dimensions, Responses., 1960-1961 (Box 8, Folder 42-43)
  - Albion Property., 1961 (Box 8, Folder 44)
  - "Agricultural Research, New Horizons for Consumers" Committee. Metz, Joseph F., 1960-1961 (Box 8, Folder 45)
  - American Agriculturist. Ingalls, Irving W.; Eastman, Edward R.; Cosline, Hugh L.; American Agriculturist Foundation., 1960-1961 (Box 8, Folder 46)
  - American Association for the Advancement of Science. Sprague, Howard B., 1960-1961 (Box 8, Folder 47)
  - American Association on Emeriti. Panunzio, Constantine., 1960-1961 (Box 8, Folder 48)
  - American Farm Bureau Federation., 1960-1961 (Box 8, Folder 49)
  - Antibiotic Residues in Milk. Kosikowski, Frank V.; Fincher, Michael G.; United States Food and Drug Administration; Pesticide residues., 1960-1961 (Box 8, Folder 50)
  - Agricultural Science Youth Program., 1960-1961 (Box 8, Folder 51)
  - Atmospheric Sciences Research Center., 1960-1961 (Box 8, Folder 52)
  - Atomic Energy Commission. United States Atomic Energy Commission., 1960-1961 (Box 8, Folder 53)
  - B Miscellaneous. Beneway, Frank W.; Noon, Francis R.; Bennett, Charles Dana; Vegetable industry., 1960-1961 (Box 8, Folder 54)
  - Bankers School of Architecture. New York State Bankers Association; Bankers School of Architecture., 1960-1961 (Box 8, Folder 55)
  - Baumel, C. Phillip., 1960-1961 (Box 8, Folder 56)
  - Brazilian Contract, Sao Paulo. Berlinck, Cyro; Davis, William E.; Sao Paulo Univ.; International Cooperation Administration., 1960-1961 (Box 8, Folder 57)
  - C Miscellaneous. Campbell Soup Company; Chemagro Corporation; Cornell Countryman., 1960-1961 (Box 8, Folder 58)
  - Cherry Producers Marketing Cooperative, Great Lakes. Freeman, Berkley I.; Fruit industry., 1960-1961 (Box 8, Folder 59)
  - Christmas Tree Growers School. Cook, Cleland C.; New York Christmas Tree Growers Association., 1960-1961 (Box 8, Folder 60)
  - Civil Defense. Morse, True D.; United States Atomic Energy Commission; Radioactivity., 1960-1961 (Box 8, Folder 61)
  - Chautauqua Lake Association., 1960-1961 (Box 8, Folder 62)
  - College-Agricultural Teacher Advisory Committee., 1960-1961 (Box 8, Folder 63)
  - Consulting Policies, Other Institutions. Shirley, Hardy L.; New York State College of Forestry., 1960-1961 (Box 8, Folder 64)
  - Colleges and Universities. Peterson, Maurice L.; Briggs, Fred N.; Reciprocal Meat Conference., 1960-1961 (Box 8, Folder 65)
  - D Miscellaneous. Tucker, Lester E.; Donlon, Mary H.; Dean, Arthur H.; Dairymen's League Cooperative Association; Dow Chemical Company; New York milkshed., 1960-1961 (Box 8, Folder 66)
  - Dairy Herd Improvement Association. Turk, Kenneth L., 1960-1961 (Box 8, Folder 67)
  - Dairy Herd Improvement Cooperative., 1960-1961 (Box 8, Folder 68)
  - Council on Economic and Cultural Affairs, Inc. Wharton, C.R., 1960-1961 (Box 8, Folder 69)
  - James E. Dewey. Morse, Roger A.; Dewey, James E.; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept, of Entomology., 1960-1961 (Box 8, Folder 70)
  - Duck Research Laboratory. Leary, John G.; Long Island Duck Research Cooperative., 1960-1961 (Box 8, Folder 71)
  - E Miscellaneous. York, John C.; Eastman, Edward R.; Eastern States Farmers1 Exchange; Council on Rural Education., 1960-1961 (Box 8, Folder 72)
  - Epsilon Sigma Phi. Smurthwaite, Georgiana H., 1960-1961 (Box 8, Folder 73)
  - Entomological Societies. Entomological Society of America., 1960-1961 (Box 8, Folder 74)
  - Empire Livestock Marketing Cooperative., 1960-1961 (Box 8, Folder 75)
  - Eastman Stage. Peabody, Eric., 1960-1961 (Box 8, Folder 76)
  - Entomological Society of America, Eastern Branch. Entomological Society of America., 1960-1961 (Box 8, Folder 77)
  - Exhibits., 1961 (Box 8, Folder 78)
  - Eastern New York Commodity Committee., 1960-1961 (Box 8, Folder 79)
  - Farm and Home Administration., 1960-1961 (Box 8, Folder 80)
  - Foreign Technical Cooperation Committee. Wellman, Harry R., 1960-1961 (Box 8, Folder 81)
  - F Miscellaneous. Cameron, Gordon; Fraleigh, Elmore; Fenton, William N.; Bennett, Charles Dana; Farm Credit Banks of Springfield., 1960-1961 (Box 8, Folder 82)
  - Farm Electrification Council. Ginna, Robert E.; New York Farm Electrification Council., 1960-1961 (Box 8, Folder 83)
  - Farm Forum. Yunker, Carl., 1960-1961 (Box 8, Folder 84)
  - Federal Milk Marketing Order Committee. Spencer, Leland., 1960-1961 (Box 8, Folder 85)
  - United States Dept, of Health, Education and Welfare, Food and Drug Administration. Flemming, Arthur S.; Stephens, M.R.; Pesticide Residues., 1960-1961 (Box 8, Folder 86)
  - Forestry. Jahn, Edwin C.; Shirley, Hardy L.; New York State College of Forestry; New York State Forest Practice Board; New York Forest Industries Council., 1960-1961 (Box 8, Folder 87)
  - Foundation Grants. Carnegie Corporation., 1960-1961 (Box 8, Folder 88)
  - Foreign Scholars Available for Remunerative Positions. Conference Board of Associated Research Councils., 1960-1961 (Box 8, Folder 89)
  - Fall-Out Shelter. United States Office of Civil and Defense Mobilization., 1960-1961 (Box 8, Folder 90)
  - Faculty Senate of State University of New York. Donaldson, Robert R.; SUNY, Faculty Senate., 1960-1961 (Box 8, Folder 91)
  - Governor's Office. Rockefeller, Nelson A., 1960-1961 (Box 8, Folder 92)
  - Governor's Milk Marketing Committee. Spencer, Leland; Rockefeller, Nelson A.; Hedlund, Glenn W., 1960-1961 (Box 8, Folder 93)
  - I Miscellaneous. Blejec, Ivan; IBM; International Paper Company; International Rescue Committee., 1960-1961 (Box 8, Folder 94)
  - Independent Milk Producers' Guide. Kennedy, W. Keith., 1960-1961 (Box 8, Folder 95)
  - International Congress of Crop Protection., 1960-1961 (Box 8, Folder 96)
  - International Minerals and Chemicals Corporation. White, Nelson C., 1960-1961 (Box 8, Folder 97)
  - J Miscellaneous. Jones, Bruce P., 1960-1961 (Box 8, Folder 98)
  - K Miscellaneous. Beach, Robert A.; Kiplinger Agricultural Letters., 1960-1961 (Box 8, Folder 99)
  - L Miscellaneous. Lee, B. Burdette; Donald Lerch and Company, Inc., 1960-1961 (Box 8, Folder 100)
  - American Assn. of Land Grant Colleges and State Universities. Peacock, N.D.; Volk, N.J., 1960-1961 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - M Miscellaneous. Morris, Fred B.; McGovern, George., 1960-1961 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Middle States Association of Colleges and Secondary Schools., 1960 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - McDonald Farms. McDonald, James M.; Trimberger, George W.; Sly, K.C.; J.M. McDonald Foundation; McDonald Farms., 1960-1961 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Milk Marketing. Spencer, Leland; Milk marketing., 1960-1961 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Monroe Apple. Adams, Morton., 1960 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - N Miscellaneous. National Safety Council; National Livestock and Meat Board; National Institute of Animal Agriculture., 1960-1961 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Natural Areas. Swanson, George T., 1960-1961 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - National Agricultural Chemicals Association., 1960-1961 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - National Canners Association. Mahoney, Charles H., 1960-1961 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - National Grange. Battles, Roy., 1960-1961 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - National Study on Agribusiness Education. Miller, Paul A.; Watkins, Thomas C., 1960-1961 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - National Study on Agribusiness Education., 1960-1961 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - New York Foundation Seed Stocks Cooperative. Bradley, R.H., 1960-1961 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - New York State Nurserymen's Association. Kirk, Edwin W., 1960-1961 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - New York Cherry Growers Association. Corey, Fred P.; Fruit industry; Mechanical harvesting., 1960-1961 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - New York Farm Bureau. Foster, Edward S., 1960-1961 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - New York State Agricultural Society. Milliman, Thomas E.; Youngs, Arthur V., 1960-1961 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - State Fair, Policy Statement. Bond, Maurice C.; New York State Fair., 1961 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Directors of Northeast Agricultural Experiment Stations, Minutes. Personius, Catherine J., 1960-1961 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Northeastern Deans and Directors of Resident Instruction in Agriculture, Annual Spring Conference. Cobble, J.W., 1960-1961 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - New York State Seed Association. White, Lyman., 1960-1961 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - New York State Grange. Smith, Leland D.; Stanley, Harold M., 1960-1961 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - New York State Horticultural Society. LaMont, Thomas E.; Mechanical harvesting; Fruit industry., 1960-1961 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - New York Foundation Seed Potato Farm. Uihlein, Henry; Evans, H.J.; Kennedy, W. Keith; New York State Foundation Seed Stocks Cooperative; Uihlein Farm; Empire State Potato Club; Potato industry., 1960-1961 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - New York State Flower Growers. Brookins, Harold B., 1960-1961 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - New York State Council of Farmer Cooperatives., 1960-1961 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - New York State Canners and Freezers Association. Sherman, William H., 1960-1961 (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - New York State Association of Agricultural Agents. Prendergast, William., 1960-1961 (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - New York Artificial Breeders' Cooperative. Crumm, Charles J., 1960-1961 (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - New York Certified Seed Growers Cooperative. Bradley, R.H., 1960-1961 (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - New York State Conference Board of Farm Organizations., 1960-1961 (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - New York State Dept, of Agriculture and Markets. Wickham, Donald J.; Dalrymple, Daniel M.; DDT., 1960-1961 (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - Institution Farmers Conference. Gilbert, George R.; Hanks, Elton K., 1960-1961 (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - State of New York, Bills. MacCrate, Robert., 1960-1961 (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - New York State Division of the Budget. Robert, Albert B.; Hurd, T. Norman., 1960-1961 (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - New York State Dept, of Conservation. Wilm, Harold G.; Swanson, Gustav A.; Heacox, Cecil E., 1960-1961 (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - New York State Education Dept. Kille, Frank R.; Fretwell, Elbert K.; Sutliff, R.C.S., 1960-1961 (Box 9, Folder 38)
  - New York State Agricultural and Technical Institutes. Wheeler, Ray L.; Foote, Norman H.; SUNY. T n c ^"* T t" 111* o c, 1960-1961 (Box 9, Folder 39)
  - New York State Fish and Wildlife Management Board. Cheatum, E.L., 1960-1961 (Box 9, Folder 40)
  - New York State Dept, of Health., 1960-1961 (Box 9, Folder 41)
  - New York State Senate. Gordon, Janet Hill; Erwin, Austin W., 1960-1961 (Box 9, Folder 42)
  - New York State Assembly., 1960-1961 (Box 9, Folder 43)
  - 0 Miscellaneous. Osorio, Jose M., 1960-1961 (Box 9, Folder 44)
  - Omnibus Farm Bill. Spencer, Leland., 1960-1961 (Box 9, Folder 45)
  - Oneida-Mohawk Dairy Farm Tour. Van Laak, John W.; Cunningham, Lowell C., 1960-1961 (Box 9, Folder 46)
  - Overseas Training Program. Friedman, Julian R., 1959-1961 (Box 9, Folder 47)
  - P Miscellaneous. Prosser, Arthur E.; Pirnie, Alexander; Paarlberg, Don; Poultry industry; Food For Peace., 1960-1961 (Box 9, Folder 48)
  - Pesticide Residue Laboratory. Hand, David B.; Pesticides., 1960-1961 (Box 9, Folder 49)
  - Pesticide Residue Committee. Pesticide Residue Laboratories; Chemical residues., 1960-1961 (Box 9, Folder 50)
  - Poultry Industry Meeting, 5 DEC 1960. Poultry industry., 1960-1961 (Box 9, Folder 51)
  - Poultry Industry Meeting, 5 DEC 1960. Hedlund, Glenn W.; Huttar, John C; Grange League Federation; Poultry industry., 1960-1961 (Box 9, Folder 52)
  - Potato Foundation Seed Stock and Certification Program. New York Certified Seed Growers Cooperative; Potato industry., 1960 (Box 9, Folder 53)
  - Programs., 1960-1961 (Box 9, Folder 54)
  - Public Law. Watkins, Thomas C., 1960 (Box 9, Folder 55)
  - Q Miscellaneous. Quebec Dept, of Agriculture., 1960-61 (Box 9, Folder 56)
  - R Miscellaneous. Reimen, Williams A.; Rockcastle, Verne N.; Rural New York., 1960-1961 (Box 9, Folder 57)
  - Rockefeller Foundation. Wernimont, Kenneth; Rockefeller Foundation., 1960-1961 (Box 9, Folder 58)
  - S Miscellaneous. Stanley, Harold M.; Skeffington, Leo B.; Shell Chemical Company; Saga Food Service; New York State Agricultural Businessmen's Council; National Academy of Sciences -National Research Council, Committee on Educational Policy in Agriculture., 1960-1961 (Box 9, Folder 59)
  - Shell Oil Company. Lykken, Louis., 1960-1961 (Box 9, Folder 60)
  - Sigma Xi. Shantz, Edgar M., 1960-1961 (Box 9, Folder 61)
  - Soil Bank. Rice, John V.B., 1960-1961 (Box 9, Folder 62)
  - SPICE, State Poultry Industry Cooperative Effort. New York State Poultry Industry Cooperative Effort. Johndrew, O.F.; Poultry industry., 1960-1961 (Box 9, Folder 63)
  - Soil Conservation Districts News., 1960-1961 (Box 9, Folder 64)
  - Saint Lawrence Seaway., 1960-1961 (Box 9, Folder 65)
  - Summer Session and Extramural Courses., 1960-1961 (Box 9, Folder 66)
  - State University of New York. SUNY., 1960-1961 (Box 9, Folder 67)
  - Student Practice. Shapley, S. Reuben., 1959-1960 (Box 9, Folder 68)
  - SUNY, Charles H. Foster, Controller. Foster, Charles H., 1960-1961 (Box 9, Folder 69)
  - SUNY, Thomas H. Hamilton, President. Hamilton, Thomas H.; SUNY; SUNY Administrative Conference., 1960-1961 (Box 9, Folder 70)
  - T Miscellaneous. Todd, Walter L., 1960-1961 (Box 9, Folder 71)
  - Teachers of Agriculture Advisory Committee. Stutz, Frederick H.; Watkins, Thomas C., 1960-1961 (Box 9, Folder 72)
  - Tennessee Valley Authority. Allbaugh, Leland G.; Tennessee Valley Authority., 1960-1961 (Box 9, Folder 73)
  - Tompkins County Fair Committee. Smith, Ralph C., 1960-1961 (Box 9, Folder 74)
  - U Miscellaneous. Union Carbide Company; United Fund., 1960-1961 (Box 9, Folder 75)
  - Universities and Colleges. American Assn. of Land Grant Colleges and State Universities., 1960-1961 (Box 9, Folder 76)
  - United Fruit Company. Hobson, Jesse E., 1960-1961 (Box 9, Folder 77)
  - United States Dept, of Agriculture. Benson, Ezra Taft; Hearne, Cannon C.; Freeman, Orville L.; United States Dept, of Agriculture, Agricultural Research Service., 1960-1961 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - United States Dept, of Agriculture, Agricultural Research Service, State Experiment Stations Division., 1960-1961 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - United States Dept, of Agriculture, Plant, Soil and Nutrition Laboratory. Wadleigh, Cecil H., 1960-1961 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - United States Dept, of Agriculture, State Emergency Planning Committee., 1960 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - United States Dept, of the Interior, Fish and Wildlife Service., 1960-1961 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - United States Savings Bond Program. Munro, Stanley E., 1960-1961 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - V Miscellaneous. Volgenau, Robert H.; Velsicol Chemical Corporation., 1960-1961 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Vegetable Commodity Committee, Orange County., 1960-1961 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Vegetable Growers' Commodity Committee, Nassau County., 1960-1961 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - W Miscellaneous. Wheeler, Ray L.; Adirondack League Club., 1960-1961 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Workmen's Compensation Insurance. Hedlund, Glenn W.; Catherwood, Martin P., 1960-1961 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - XYZ Miscellaneous. Zucker, Isabel., 1961 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - President's Report. Malott, Deane W., 1961-1962 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Dean's Meeting with President Malott. Malott, Deane W., 1961-1962 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Dean of Students. Cornell University, Office of Dean of Students., 1961-1962 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Cornell Aeronautical Laboratory., 1961-1962 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Agricultural College Council, 21 May 1962. New York State College of Agriculture, Advisory Council., 1961-1962 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Agricultural Business Curriculum. Ott, Leland E., 1961-1962 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Marketing Conference Notes. Ott, Leland E., 1961-1962 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Agricultural Progress Days. Wallace, Henry A.; Freeman, Orville L.; Alpha Zeta; New York State College of Agriculture, Agricultural Progress Days., 1961-1962 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Agricultural Progress Days. McGovern, George; Ward, William B.; Poppensiek, George C.; New York State College of Agriculture, Agricultural Progress Days., 1961-1962 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Agricultural Progress Days Luncheon. Elliott, Lloyd H.; New York State College of Agriculture, Agricultural Progress Days., 1961-1962 (Box 10, Folder 22-23)
  - Alumni Association, College of Agriculture. Hopper, Nelson F.; Gittins, Thomas W.; New York State College of Agriculture, Alumni Association., 1961-1962 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Annual Reports. Kennedy, W. Keith., 1961-1962 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Botany. Banks, Harlan P.; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept, of Botany., 1961-1962 (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Buildings., 1961-1962 (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Buildings and Properties. Weinhold, Julius F., 1961-1962 (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - Calendar of Events., 1961-1962 (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Campus Store., 1961-1962 (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Claims, Miscellaneous., 1961-1962 (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - Commencement Procedures.., 1962 (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - Cornell Contract Groups., 1961-1962 (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - Cornell University Council. Zwingle, J.L.; Cornell University, Council., 1961-1962 (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - Cornell Countryman. Brody, Jane B.; Cornell Countryman., 1961-1962 (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - College Dairy Committee., 1961-1962 (Box 10, Folder 36)
  - Argentine Exchange Student. Poludniak, Norman; Patrick, George F.; Camberos, Hector R.; Hertel, John P.; Univ. of Buenos Aires., 1961-1962 (Box 10, Folder 37)
  - Extension Service. Bond, Maurice C.; New York State Cooperative Extension Service., 1961-1962 (Box 10, Folder 38)
  - Extension Service, Law Change. Bond, Maurice C; New York State Cooperative Extension Service., 1961-1962 (Box 10, Folder 39)
  - Dutchess County Extension Service. Adams, J. Alfred; Bond, Maurice C.; New York State Cooperative Extension Service., 1961-1962 (Box 10, Folder 40)
  - Madison County Extension Service. New York State Cooperative Extension Service., 1961-1962 (Box 10, Folder 41)
  - Extension Food Processing. Barton, Donald W., 1961 (Box 10, Folder 42)
  - Special Extension Service. New York State Cooperative Extension Service., 1961-1962 (Box 10, Folder 43)
  - Project M. New York State Cooperative Extension Service., 1961-1962 (Box 10, Folder 44)
  - Operation Advance. New York State Cooperative Extension Service., 1961-1962 (Box 10, Folder 45)
  - Conference Facilities Information. Risley, Robert F., 1961-1962 (Box 10, Folder 46)
  - Foreign Visitors Contact Office. Morris, Fred B., 1961-1962 (Box 10, Folder 47)
  - Facilities Projected for Construction or Acquisition by 1970 or Sooner. Peterson, Arthur H.; Watkins, Thomas C., 1961-1962 (Box 10, Folder 48)
  - Faculty of the College of Agriculture. New York State College of Agriculture, Faculty., 1961-1962 (Box 10, Folder 49)
  - University Faculty. Mackesey, Thomas W.; Cornell University, University Faculty., 1961-1962 (Box 10, Folder 50-51)
  - University Faculty Committee on Long-Range Planning. Watkins, Thomas C., 1961-1962 (Box 10, Folder 52-53)
  - Draft of a Policy Statement Concerning Private Consulting Privileges of Faculty in the New York State College of Agriculture. Consulting., 1962 (Box 10, Folder 54)
  - College Fleet. Murphy, John C., 1961-1962 (Box 10, Folder 55)
  - Cornell Food Research Committee., 1961-1962 (Box 10, Folder 56)
  - Food Technology Committee. Personius, Catherine J.; Hand, David B.; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept, of Food Science and Technology., 1961-1962 (Box 10, Folder 57)
  - Foreign Students. Morris, Fred B.; Williams, David B.; Kizilbash, Mehdi; Cornell University, Foreign Student Office., 1961-1962 (Box 10, Folder 58)
  - Freshman Orientation., 1961-1962 (Box 10, Folder 59)
  - A.W. Gibson. Gibson, Anson W., 1961-1962 (Box 10, Folder 60)
  - Graduate School. Boynton, Damon; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept, of Botany; Cornell University, Graduate School; Cornell University, Sage Graduate Center., 1961-1962 (Box 10, Folder 61)
  - Graduates, September and February. Gross, Carol P., 1961-1962 (Box 10, Folder 62)
  - History of the College of Agriculture. Colman, Gould P.; Stutz, Frederick H.; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept, of Rural Education; New York State College of Agriculture, Oral History Project., 1961-1962 (Box 10, Folder 63)
  - Home Economics. Canoyer, Helen G.; Wood, Mary B.; New York State College of Home Economics, Student-Faculty Committee., 1961-1962 (Box 10, Folder 64)
  - Home Economics. Canoyer, Helen G.; Donlon, Mary H.; New York State College of Home Economics., 1961-1962 (Box 10, Folder 65)
  - Home Economics Advisory Council Meeting, 3-4 May 1962. New York State College of Home Economics; New York State College of Home Economics, Advisory Council., 1961-1962 (Box 10, Folder 66)
  - Home Economics Council. New York State College of Home Economics., 1961-1962 (Box 10, Folder 67)
  - Ho-Nun-De-Kah. Hertel, John P.; Shapley, Allan E.; New York State College of Agriculture, Ho-Nun-De-Kah., 1961-1962 (Box 10, Folder 68)
  - New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations., 1961-1962 (Box 10, Folder 69)